你知道我喜欢人哪一点吗
You know what I like about people?
会排队
They stack so well.
我来收拾吧
Let me get this for you.
-报纸还要吗  -不了
- Want the paper? - No.
太多了
This is too much.
差得远呢
It's not half enough.
谢谢你为我开店
Thanks for opening up for me.
你知道我随时欢迎你来
Any time, day or night. You know that.
这个城市的每个人都在精心地改头换面
In a town where everyone's so carefully reinventing themselves,
而弗莱迪的可贵之处
what I like about Freddy
就是他甚至不装作要改变
is that he doesn't even pretend to change.
我要迟到了
Ooh. I'm late.
我每周二都会和议长及多数党领袖一起
Every Tuesday I sit down with the speaker and the majority leader
商讨一周的事宜
to discuss the week's agenda.
说是"商讨"可能不太准确
Well, discuss is probably the wrong word.
他们谈话  而我安静地坐着
They talk while I sit quietly
想象他们淡腌过的脸在煎锅中炸
and imaging their lightly salted faces frying in a skillet.
瓦斯奎兹肯定吓得拉裤子了
Vasquez must be shitting herself.
别说她  沃克肯定也是
Shitting herself, when Walker is shitting himself
俩人的屎都摞一起了
and shoveling his shit on her shit.
鲍勃  我还想吃东西呢
Bob, I'm planning on eating.
有备用的法案吗
Do we have a backup on the docket?
你在处理吧  弗兰克
You're on that, right, Frank?
是的  我和我的团队...
Yeah, I'm working with my staff--
共和党会为此对我们穷追烂打
Republicans are gonna ram this up our ass.
换了我也会这么做
I would if I was them.
就算众议院勉强通过
Why, even if we squeak it through the house,
参议院也会百般刁难
watch them mangle it in the senate.
国会投票前要就法案进行辩论  人数少的党派可找一个议员一直在台上讲
使法案不能进入投票  从而阻止一个法案通过
或阻挠议事
Or filibuster.
好吧  如果是那样...
Why, sure, if it looks anything like this...
我不明白沃克为什么
I don't know why Walker's
要对付一头横冲直撞的大象
trying to tackle a charging elephant.
真是疯了
It's madness.
各位议员  抱歉打扰了
Congressmen, sorry to interrupt,
我看见你们在这儿
but I saw you sitting over here--
雷米  两位  这是雷米・丹顿
Remy. Gentlemen, this is Remy Danton.
雷米  这位是博奇议长和鲍勃...
Remy, this is Speaker Birch and Congress--
我知道  议长先生  议员先生
I'm well aware. Mr. Speaker, Congressman.
雷米刚成为格兰顿-希尔的合伙人
Remy just made partner at Glendon Hill.
格兰顿-希尔可挺不错啊
Glendon Hill? Great team over there.
-恭喜  -谢谢
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
有多久没提拔合伙人了
When was the last time they added a partner?
挺久了
It's been a while.
他们一看就知道谁是好手
Well, they know a winner when they see one.
雷米是我手下最好的新闻发言人
Remy was the best press secretary I ever had.
那你怎么放他走了
Why did you let him go?
我没有  他们把他挖走了
I didn't. They stole him away.
你们有哪些客户
What accounts do you have?
桑科工业是我的主要客户
San Corp Industries is my main one.
我负责他们公司
I run that account now.
好了  那我就先走了
Anyhow, I'll let you get back to it.
再次抱歉打扰了
Sorry again to interrupt.
没关系
No problem.
很高兴见到二位
Very nice to meet you both.
-真好  -说客越来越年轻了
- Nice. - Lobbyists keep getting younger and younger.
他挣得大概比我们加起来还多
He's probably making more than all of us combined.
先生们  这顿算我的
Gentlemen, this one's on me.
我去买单
I'm gonna track down that check.
格兰顿-希尔为桑科工业做说客
Glendon Hill fronts San Corp Industries.
桑科的天然气做得有声有色
San Corp is deep into natural gas.
但我才不在乎天然气
I don't give a hoot about natural gas,
我有67位副手
but I have 67 deputy whips,
他们都需要钱来赢得竞选
and they all need cash to win races.
桑科帮我买到了忠诚
San Corp helps me purchase loyalty,
也指望我以忠心相报
and in return they expect mine.
我知道这很下作
It's degrading, I know,
但利润如此丰厚
but when the tit's that big,
谁都想分一杯羹
everybody gets in line.
告诉他们一切尽在掌握之中
Tell them I'm on top of it.
这可打发不了我
I need more than that.
你知道我不会在这种事上犯错  雷米
You are well aware that I do not drop the ball on things like this, Remy.
你的承诺  弗兰克
Promises, Frank.
当选国务卿  阿根廷的近海开采合同
Secretary of State, Argentine and off shore drilling contracts--
我解决问题之后再谈
Talk to me when I've solved the problem.
现在别浪费我的时间
Don't waste my time when I'm working on solving the problem.
事关数十亿资金
When there's billions on the line,
你不能不回我电话
You can't not call me back.
我也不能做鸵鸟
I can't not show up.
好吧  多谢费心
Fine. Thank you for your diligence.
我们捐了上千万给民主党竞选委员会
Eight figures to you and the D triple C.
以你命名的图书馆花了六百万
6 million to build that library of yours in your name.
我知道
I know.
别逼得他们下回去资助你的对手
Don't make them throw money at your challenger next cycle.
你说得很清楚了
You've made your point.
是吗  希望如此
Have I? I hope so.
真是浪费啊
Such a waste of talent.
为了钱而放弃权力
He chose money over power--
这个城市里  几乎人人都犯了这个错
In this town, a mistake nearly everyone makes.
大型现代房屋  缺乏个性  和当地建筑格格不入
金钱是萨拉索塔的巨无霸豪宅
Money is the McMansion in Sarasota
保质期就只有十年
that starts falling apart after ten years.
权力是古老的石砌建筑
Power is the old stone building
能屹立数百年
that stands for centuries.
我要怎么尊重这都不懂的人
I cannot respect someone who doesn't see the difference.
这是什么
What am I looking at?
《威廉姆斯公报》
The Williams register.
-哪个  -那个大学
- Williams? - College.
78年9月
September '78.
让我看这个做什么
And why am I looking at it?
那篇社论
The editorial.
挺无聊的
Not that interesting.
迈克尔・科恩曾在威廉姆斯念书
Michael Kern went to Williams.
看报头
Check out the masthead.
还有这个
And then there's this.
站不住
It's thin.
那家伙太讨喜了  屎都是香的
The guy's a unicorn. He pisses rainbows.
-你觉得这个能吸引眼球  -你可以
- You think we can get traction with this? - I think you could.
琳达・瓦斯奎兹的电话
Linda Vasquez is on the phone.
没想到她这么久才打来
Ah, I'm surprised it took her this long.
才9点06分
It's only 6 past 9:00.
那她肯定三小时前就看过《先驱报》了
Which means she read the Herald 3 hours ago
然后被总统骂了两个半小时
and spent the past 2 1/2 getting reamed by the president.
跟她说我就来
Tell her I'm on my way.
你本该看着唐纳德的
You were supposed to keep Donald in line.
你向我保证
You assured me that you--
他推动这项议程有25年了
25 years he's been pushing this particular agenda.
他这就是护犊子
We got between the mother bear and her cub.
只是个小挫折罢了
It's a setback. That's all.
这是我们就职首日
On our first day in office.
琳达  我为四位总统工作过
Linda, I've worked with four presidents.
这么大的法案  挫折在所难免
Setbacks are a dime a dozen with a bill of this size.
弗兰克  你要是控制不住局面
Frank, if you can't control this--
我不喜欢被人死死盯着  琳达
I don't take well to being micromanaged, Linda.
你是要一边打理白宫  还干我的活儿吗
You want to do my job for me and run the White House?
祝你好运  我绝不阻拦
Good luck. I won't stand in your way.
好吧  弗兰克  这事你解决
Okay, Frank. Fine. This is yours now.
要是在一百天内  法案不能进行投票
If this thing can't make it to the floor in the first 100 days,
我就让你去跟总统解释
then I'll let you explain to the president
他怎么对美国人民失信了
why he lied to the American people.
我要回去干活了
I'm gonna get back to work.
请便
Please do.
这事真该放在周五
Well, we really should be doing this on a Friday
而不是周三
instead of a Wednesday.
要是周五的话
If we do it on a Friday,
-大家周末就能...  -好吧  那就周五
- people have the weekend-- - Fine. We'll do it on Friday.
文件都弄好了吗
Is all the paperwork ready?
部分老人比较棘手
Some of the more senior people are trickier.
需要离职金
There's severance.
应该没有什么法律问题吧
But we shouldn't run into any legal issues.
不会的  我们签的都是自由雇佣合同
No, no. We use at-will employment contracts across the board.
周五一来就着手这事
Well, get started first thing Friday.
午餐前搞定所有离职面谈
I want all of the exit interviews done by lunch.
克莱尔  我就是觉得这是个错误
Claire, I just can't help but think that this is a mistake.
我们已经谈过这个问题了  伊芙琳
We've discussed this already, Evelyn.
我知道  但出于良心
I know, I know, but I just have to say it
我必须说出来
for the sake of my conscience.
我觉得你在摧毁
I think that you are dismantling
我们过去十年建立的一切
what we have built over the past ten years,
而我
and I--
我觉得你的处理方式
and I think the way you're handling this is...
很残忍
is cruel.
对我也不容易  伊芙琳
It's not easy, Evelyn.
但我必须这么做
But it's necessary.
你一直让我实话实说
You have always asked me to be honest with you.
这是我们共事的基础
It's how we work together.
我有不同意见  就说出来
I disagree with something, I say it.
我对此完全不赞同
Well, I disagree 100%.
求你  克莱尔  别这样做
Please, Claire, don't do this.
我尊重你的意见  伊芙琳
I respect your opinion, Evelyn,
我也很感谢你愿意告诉我
and I appreciate you sharing it with me,
但我不会改变主意的
but I'm not going to change my mind.
周五
Friday, then.
你说了算
If that's what you want.
这是一项重大改革  全面改革
This is major reform, a complete overhaul.
一般都要几个月呢
That would usually take months.
我们只有几天  没有几个月
Well, we only have days, not months.
但想想这个过程  我们不能随便...
But think about the process. We can't just change--
我询问我的同事  你们的上司
When I ask my colleagues, your bosses,
教育界最聪明的人是谁
who are the smartest minds in education,
千挑万选  选中了你们
out of hundreds, we arrived at you--
这间房里的六位
the six of you in this room.
我知道任务艰巨
Now, I realize it is a difficult task,
但我们现在有机会创造历史
but we have the opportunity to make history here.
我希望大家能齐心协力
And I want all of us to make it together.
祝好运  靠你们了
So good luck. We're counting on you.
第一页
Page 1.
着重号标出了
These bullet points reflect
法案的核心条款
the key planks at the center of our bill.
坐舒服了
Get comfy.
拿不出像样的初稿  就别想回家
This is your home until we have a presentable first draft.
唐纳德  今早真够呛
Donald, what a morning.
我不知道他们怎么搞到的
I have no idea how they got this.
我明确告诉手下销毁一切
I specifically told my staff to destroy everything.
-我真不知...  -那不是重点
- I can't imagine- - It doesn't matter how it happened.
过去的没法改变  只能随机应变
We can't make it unhappen, so we have to adapt.
他们不知道这只是初稿吗
Don't they realize that this is a first draft?
其实就看你是站在什么角度了
All we have here really is a perception problem.
第一印象只有一次  唐纳德
We don't get a second chance at a first impression, Donald.
你也知道  我当然站在你这边
You know that. Now, look, I'm on your side,
但琳达很生气
but Linda is furious.
她是什么意思
What's she saying?
他们要找人怪罪
They want to point fingers.
我吗
At me?
我跟她说不能这样
I told her we cannot do that.
你对立法及其重要
I mean, you are vital to this process.
唐纳德  我受够他们了
I'm up to here with them, Donald--
谎话连篇  落井下石
for lying, for turning their back on you.
我要说  去你的
You know, I'm of a mind to say screw it.
这个栽我认了
I'll fall on this grenade myself,
就气死他们
just to piss them off.
给我接CNN的约翰・金
Give me John King at CNN.
等等  弗兰克  这不是你的错
Wait, Frank. This is not your fault.
不  我们得保护你的声誉
No, we have to protect your reputation.
但是你得保证法案通过投票
But you're the man that needs to get the bill through the house.
我会...等等  我会交待我的副手
I will-- hang on. I will assign it to one of my deputies,
私下搞定  教你怎么走那个过场
quietly manage it, and I'll help guide you through the process.
我不喜欢这样
I am not comfortable with this.
那你说我们怎么办
Well, then what do you suggest we do?
烈士最渴求的
What a martyr craves more than anything
就是壮烈牺牲
is a sword to fall on,
所以  你磨好兵刃
so you sharpen the blade,
调整好角度
hold it at just the right angle,
默数三  二  一
and then 3, 2, 1--
我来
It should be me.
这是我的法案
It was my bill.
不行  唐纳德
No. Impossible. Donald,
教育事业是你毕生的心血
education has been your life's work.
实际上  我的心根本不在这儿
The truth is my heart is not in this fight.
你也知道  我不会精明算计
You know me. I'm not a wheeler dealer.
我全心投入制定政策
I can put my mind to policy,
但没什么政治手腕
but I'm no good at this brand of politics.
那要找谁替你呢
Well, if not you, then who?
应该你来  弗兰克
It should be you, Frank.
你令人敬畏  受人尊重
You're formidable. People respect you.
他们会听你的领导  让我
They will follow your lead. Let me--
让我置身事外吧
let me be on the sidelines for this.
要我考虑接受
Well, I could only consider that as an option
你得保证给我提建议
if I knew that I could still come to you for counsel.
当然  听候差遣
Of course. Whatever you need.
我内心多少庆幸泄密了
Part of me is glad this got leaked.
如果没这事最好
Well, it would have been better if it hadn't,
但至少人们知道了我的立场
but at least people know where I stand.
谢谢你  唐纳德
Thank you, Donald.
我的荣幸  弗兰克
Happy to do it, Frank.
他不知道我们找了六个孩子在隔壁
He has no idea we've got six kids in the next room
紧锣密鼓地拟定新草案
already working on a new draft.
斯坦普  何必要说出来让他伤心呢
Stamper! But why dampen his mood by telling him?
我们刚刚给了他份大礼
We just gave him a great gift--
让他能完成使命
a chance to fulfill his destiny.
为布莱斯写一份声明
Write up a statement for Blythe--
有事要谈  今晚见
退位让贤  提出新想法
stepping aside, fresh ideas,
等等  等等  给他点面子
et cetera, et cetera, and make it dignified.
他是个好人
He's a good man.
把威廉姆斯社论拿来
Oh. And bring me that Williams editorial.
收件人  佐伊・巴恩斯
经过慎重考虑和团队商议
After careful thought and discussion with my staff,
我将不再负责教育改革法案
I am relinquishing my management of the education reform act.
我仍然希望能略尽绵力
I hope to remain a part of the process,
但我将不再...
but I won't be working--
你为什么要泄露草案
Why did you leak the draft?
我不清楚怎么会泄露
I'm not exactly sure how it got leaked,
但是它代表了
but, uh, it does represent--
是从你办公室泄露出去的  对吗
It came from your office, though, correct?
是我们起草的  但我不
Uh, we wrote it, but I don't--
现在是谁负责这个法案
Who'll be managing the bill now?
弗兰克・安德伍德
Frank Underwood.
是你的决定
Was that your choice,
还是政府
or did the administration--
教室危机  唐纳德・布莱斯  泄露教育草案执笔人
弗兰克能力出众
I feel very confident
由他接手法案  我非常放心
placing the bill in Frank's capable hands.
巴恩斯小姐
Ms. Barnes.
深喉为1972年水门事件中内线的假名
你真够深喉
How very deep throat of you.
我没法帮你撵走一个总统
Well, I can't help you dispatch a president.
参议员怎么样
How about a senator?
戴维营协议:上世纪八十年代埃以签署的重要协议
关于戴维营协议的社论
The editorial on the Camp David Accords.
本报认为
"It is the opinion of this newspaper
卡特总统应要求以色列
that President Carter demand Israel
撤出约旦河西岸
withdraw all its citizens
及加沙地带的所有以色列公民
from the Gaza Strip and West Bank."
以色列自1967年以来就非法占据了该地区
"Which it has illegally occupied since 1967."
非法占据
Illegally occupied.
这话肯定能引起轰动  你说呢
That's quite an incendiary quote, don't you think?
毕竟这届政府表示
For an administration that says
中东是外交政策的重中之重
that the Middle East is its top foreign policy priority.
迈克尔・科恩
Michael Kern?
社论是他亲自执笔的吗
Did he personally write the editorial?
他是编辑
He was the editor.
但是他执笔的吗
But did he write it himself?
那这就不算新闻
Then there's no story.
我认为这是一个值得指出的问题
I'm saying it's a question worth asking.
如果他否认与这篇文章有关呢
And if he denies involvement?
那是必然  随他去
He will. Let him.
这个人正在等着正式上任国务卿
This is a man trying to be confirmed as Secretary of State.
他的一切都是新闻
Everything is a story.
可是没有直接关联
There's no direct link.
汉默施密特不会允许见报的
I can't get this past Hammerchmidt.
记住你拒绝我的这一刻
Remember this moment when you resisted me,
记住你亲口说  "那这就不算新闻"
when you said the words "Then there is no story."
好好睡一觉吧  巴恩斯小姐
Get a good night's sleep, Ms. Barnes.
明天还有你忙的
You have a big day tomorrow.
弗兰西斯
Francis?
这是什么
What is this?
你觉得像什么
What does it look like?
但地下室是我的
But the basement is mine.
我知道  这不是给我的
I know. It's not for me.
那是给谁的
So who's it for?
给你的
For you.
国会大厦有健身房
There's a gym in the Capitol.
你从来不去
Which you never use.
国事已经够我忙的了
Because I'm a tad busy running the country.
在家不用忙国事  你还要怎么说
But not at home, so now you have no excuse.
把它给我拿出去
I want it out.
试试看嘛
Give it a try first.
你是在委婉地表示我身材走样了吗
Is this your subtle way of saying that I'm out of shape?
不  我不过是认为
No, it's my way of suggesting
你的身材可以再好一点
you could be in better shape.
这句话既以退为进
That sounds both passive-aggressive
又居高临下
and condescending.
我这是以诚为进
Just plain aggressive and true.
别等我
Don't wait up for me.
你这个时间去跑步吗
Are you going running now?
对  因为我早上没跑成
Yes, because I couldn't this morning.
有个晨会
I had an early meeting.
外面那么冷  用这个怪物锻炼吧
Use the monstrosity. It's freezing out.
你先来
You break it in.
看上去像中世纪文物  不是吗
It looks positively medieval, doesn't it?
把我仅有的圣殿变成健身地牢
And to turn my only sanctuary into a fitness dungeon.
我绝不容忍
I won't have it.
国务卿提名人迈克尔・科恩首肯反以社论
站不住脚
It's a stretch.
我们没有误导读者
We're not misleading anyone.
-他的确是编辑  -他们有回应吗
- He was the editor. - Did you call for a comment?
我打了三次电话
I tried three times.
新闻发言人说他会回电
The press secretary said he'd get back to me.
-但他没回  -背景调查呢
- He didn't. - What about research?
有任何附和这篇社论的材料吗
You couldn't find anything to echo the editorial?
言论  评论文章
No quotes, no op-ed pieces?
你不觉得如果有的话
Don't you think if something like that existed,
早会有人报道了吗
someone would have printed it by now?
只有我们知道  卢卡斯
Nobody else has this, Lucas.
我觉得这算不上是新闻
I don't think there's a story here.
我没说这是新闻
I'm not saying there's a story.
我不过认为这是个应该提出的问题
All I'm saying is that there's a question that needs to be answered.
这可是国务卿提名人
This is a nominee for Secretary of State.
而我们手上有份巴以社论
We have an editorial on Palestine and Israel.
却不是他写的
Which he didn't write.
我们无法确认这点
Which we don't know he didn't write.
正是
Exactly.
不非得见报啊
We don't have to print it.
我可以扫描一份  发在网上
I could just scan the thing, stick it on a site,
然后推特网址
and tweet the link.
但那样的话  别家报纸
But if I did that, some other paper might--
行了  别那么贱
Whoa, whoa. Don't be a bitch.
我去和汤姆说
I'll talk to Tom.
我就是这个意思
That's all I was asking.
我们不能允许...
We simply can't afford to allow the--
迈克尔・科恩  国务卿提名人
我们找到一个绝佳人选
We got a guy who's almost perfect.
他是一个窝在房车里的自由意志主义瘾君子
He's a libertarian drug fiend marinating in a mobile home.
我不赞成里根总统的很多主张
I didn't agree with President Reagan on many things,
但滴入式经济的理念确实有可取之处
but there was some merit to the notion of trickle-down economics,
并且我认为滴入式外交也益处良多
and I feel there is much merit to the idea of trickle-down diplomacy.
如果我们能解决...
If we can solve...
那是我说的
Those are my lines.
一定是瓦斯奎兹告诉他的
Vasquez must have given them to him.
以色列和巴勒斯坦之间的僵局
...stalemate between Israel and Palestine,
这项成功将"滴入"
that success will trickle down
"滴入式外交"
其他穆斯林  犹太和基督教国家之间的
to a hundred other diplomatic dilemmas between Muslims,
外交困境中
Jews, Christians--
正好你提到了以色列和巴勒斯坦
I'm glad you brought up Israel and Palestine
我们直播前不久
because just before we came on the air,
我收到一篇明天将刊登在
I received an advance copy of an article
《华盛顿先驱报》头版的报道样本
that's going to be in tomorrow's washington Herald's front page
作者是佐伊・巴恩斯
and was written by Zoe Barnes,
其中她引用了一篇
and in it she quotes
刊登在《威廉姆斯公报》上的一篇社论
an editorial that ran in the Williams College register
时间为1978年九月  你时任公报总编
when you were editor back in September 1978,
其中称在加沙地带
which called the Israeli presence
和约旦河西岸居住的以色列人
in the Gaza Strip and West Bank, quote,
为"非法占据"
an illegal occupation.
-我能看下吗  -当然
- Can I see that?  - Sure.
"非法占据"是出自你手吗
Did you write those words, "Illegal occupation"?
不  我完全不记得这事
No. I have no memory of this.
你可是报纸的总编
But you were the editor of the paper.
没错  但是
Yes, but--
那没经你首肯  它无法见报
So it couldn't have gone out without your approval.
对  那是当然  但是我的下属
No, of course not, but my staff--
通常是其他人来写...
somebody else usually wrote the, uh,
之后我们还投票  如果
the, uh-- and then we'd vote, and if--
你投赞成票了吗
Did you vote for it?
说真的  乔治  我记不得了
Honestly, George, I can't remember.
这都35年了
It was 35 years ago.
这么说你不确定
So you're not sure
自己当时是否赞成这些言论
whether or not you supported these words--
我非常确信地告诉你
I can tell you without a shadow of a doubt
我没写过那些话
I did not write these words.
但当时你是那样想的吗
But were they in line with your thinking at the time?
这太荒谬了
This is ludicrous.
我知道这事有年头了  这我理解
I know it was a long time ago, I understand that.
这个就足够了  他的笑
That's all we need-- him laughing.
南茜  帮我接反诽谤联盟的丹尼斯・门德尔
Nancy, get me Dennis Mendel of the ADL.
中东地区对我国利益至关重要
The Middle East is a vital American interest.
你对中东地区的看法很重要
What you think about the Middle East is relevant.
你可以察看我的表决记录
You can look at my voting record.
每一票都站在以色列的立场上
Every single vote has been in defense of Israel--
那你什么时候改变想法的
So when did your views change?
我的意思就是
What I'm saying to you is my--
现在要紧的  乔治
What's important now, George,
是我代表
is how I have voted
科罗拉多州时投的表决票
while I have represented the great state of Colorado--
这我知道
I understand that's your position,
但很多看到这篇报道的人会认为
but a lot of other people are going to look at it and think
你当时的想法也是很重要的
what you thought then is relevant as well.
那我问你
Well, let me ask you this.
你大学之后从未改变过想法吗
Have you ever changed your views since college?
有  但我又没有被提名为国务卿
Certainly, but I'm not the nominee for Secretary of State.
就算我曾经有
Uh, even if I did have--
真是绝了
It's golden.
我也早就不再...
This has not been my views--
正中靶心
It's a bull's eye.
你刚进来时说什么来着
What were you saying when you came in?
是这样的  我找到一个人
So, ahem, I found a guy
是科恩任总编时学院的编辑人员
who was on the college editorial staff when Kern was there.
这个瘾君子
This burnout,
仍然伯克郡的一个
still pumping mimeographed manifestos
拖车公园里油印自由宣言
out of a trailer park in the Berkshires.
-你可不能去见他  -不不
- You're not planning on talking to him. - No. No.
让彼得・罗素去
Peter Russo.
很好
Good.
一对儿瘾君子  正合适
Sounds like a perfect match.
丹尼斯
Dennis.
你在看史蒂法诺普洛的节目吗
Any chance you're watching Stephanopoulos?
你努力提高辛勤的宾州人民的
You look sexy when you're improving the lives
生活水平的样子真性感
of hardworking Pennsylvanians.
是因为我在工作
Is it the improving lives,
还是因为这条迷人的运动裤
or is it these fetching sweat pants?
把电脑拿开
Why don't you move that computer out of the way?
让我鉴定一下
Let me see what that looks like.
还是用电脑挡着好
Yeah, it's better with the laptop.
一边去
Fuck off.
你对我不够关注
You're not paying enough attention to me.
在办公室  我整天都在关注你
I pay attention to you all day at the office.
我以前好像
Hey, you know, I don't think
从没见过你刷牙
I've ever seen you brush your teeth before.
-肯定见过  -应该没有
- Sure you have. - No, I don't think so.
我知道你肯定刷牙
I mean I know that you do brush,
但好像从没亲眼见过
but I don't think I've ever actually witnessed it before.
这次让你欣赏个够
Well, here it is in all its glory.
那是我的牙刷吗
Is that my toothbrush?
不知道  是吗
I don't know. Is it?
是的
Yes, it is.
-是你留下的  -彼得  真恶心
- You left it here. - Peter, gross.
得了吧
Oh, come on.
我们都交换过多少体液了
We've exchanged plenty of fluids by now.
别别别
Hey, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不要  有牙膏
No. Toothpaste.
没有牙膏  让我放纵一下
It's not toothpaste. I'm ravished.
别啊
No.
快去接
Go get it.
这个必须接
I have to take this.
我是罗素
This is Russo.
现在12点53分
Yeah. Right now it's 12:53.
好好好
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
我得走了
I have to go.
有什么事吗
Is everything okay?
工作上的事
It's work stuff.
什么工作上的事
What kind of work stuff?
维林斯基议员
Congressman Wallinski.
想谈谈我们发去的税收鼓励方案
He wants to go over the tax incentive stuff we sent him.
彼得  现在是凌晨1点
Peter, it's 1:00 in the morning.
彼得
Hey, Peter.
明天要开会
I have meetings tomorrow.
有个委员会的听证会
I have a committee hearing.
国会没有你照样运转
Congress will survive without you.
目的地和指示
Address, directions.
这是以你的名义订的电子票
There's an e-ticket in your name.
飞机六点半起飞
Your flight leaves at 6:30.
你该出发去机场了
You should head to the airport.
是弗兰克的意思吧
This is coming from Frank?
不  没有人下指令
No. This is coming from no one.
你得了流感  要请病假
You have the flu, and you're calling in sick.
-那是什么  -什么是什么
- What's that? - What's what?
是吻痕吗
Is that a hickey?
你又去拈花惹草了吗
Are you whoring around again?
没有  我有女朋友的
No. I have a girlfriend.
你是指你的办公室恋情吧
You mean your little office romance.
你知道些什么
What do you know about that?
要说我对你生活的了解  彼得
When it comes to your life, Peter, and what I know about it,
你应该当做我无所不知
you should assume that there's no such thing as a secret.
保持联系
Stay in touch.
有事打我手机  千万别打到办公室
You call me on my cell, never at the office.
祝你好运
Good luck.
别手下留情
Knock 'em dead, tiger.
大伙怎么样
How are we?
累瘫了  没干劲了
Overtired, under-caffeinated,
不过有进展
but we're making progress.
还有不到一周
Less than a week to go.
是啊  我们会尽力
Yeah. We'll do our best.
-你再说一遍  -我们会搞定的
- You'll what? - We'll get it done.
谁去开个窗  难闻死了
Somebody open a window. It's rancid in here.
六个人半星期不洗澡就是这样
That is what happens when six people don't shower for half a week.
除了除臭剂还需要什么
Anything you need other than deodorant?
关于绩效标准
Yeah, this performance standards thing.
-教师工会会...  -留着吧
- The teachers unions are gonna-- - Leave it in.
-可以删的  -工会那边交给我
- But we could delete it. - I'll handle the unions.
还有别的吗
What else? Anything?
夫妻探访
Conjugal visits?
我继续干活儿了
I'll get back to work.
-南茜  -来了
- Nancy. - Coming.
接下来什么安排
What do I have next?
2点10分到35分与选民通话
Constituent calls from 2:10 to 2:35,
募资到3点50分  4点副党鞭会议
fundraising until 3:50, deputy caucus at 4:00.
-通话名单在哪  -在你桌上
- The call list? - It's on your desk.
-会议备忘录呢  -在通话名单旁边
- My briefing for the caucus? -Next to the call list.
去过会议室了吗
Have you been in the conference room?
周末把那儿蒸汽清洁一下
Have it steam cleaned over the weekend.
另外  给那几个可怜的孩子买些除臭剂
In the meantime, get those poor kids some Febreze or something.
臭得像迷你动物园
It's like a petting zoo.
你必须得看看
You gotta see this.
但当时你是那样想的吗
But were they in line with your thinking at the time?
对以评论引国务卿提名人科恩爆笑  门德尔认为科恩是反犹份子
巴以问题
We do not consider the issue
不是什么好笑的事
of Israel and Palestine a laughing matter.
他还称以色列"非法"
And he calls Israel illegal.
这是反犹思想  而且大错特错
Well, he's an anti-semite, and he is wrong.
如果任命这样的人
We would have grave, grave concerns
来做国务卿  我们将十分忧虑
about appointing such a man our next Secretary of State.
得来全不费工夫
It's too easy.
唯一真相  罗伊・科佩尼科的博客和想法
汽车租赁行
罗伊  你好
Roy, hi.
我是彼得・罗素  罗素议员
My name is Peter Russo. Congressman Russo.
我想和你谈谈
I'd like to just speak to you for just a...
先生
Sir?
你要么是在撒谎  那就滚蛋
Either you're lying, and you can fuck off;
要么没在撒谎  那就更得滚蛋
or you're telling the truth, and you can absolutely fuck off.
我看了你的网站
I saw your web site.
我是你的粉丝
I'm a fan.
还给你带了礼物
And I brought you something.
宝贝  去把衣服穿上
Hey, babe, put some clothes on.
-什么  -有客人来了
- What? - We got a guest.
那又怎样  你好啊
So? Hey.
去把衣服穿上
Put some clothes on.
要加冰吗
Ice or no ice?
-不加  -很好
- Uh, no ice. - Good.
我们没有冰了
We don't have any.
该死  艾柯  我叫你把...
Fuck. Echo, I told you to put the--
没关系
It's okay. It's okay.
你替我保密  我也替你保密
I'll keep your secret if you keep mine.
你说你是国会议员
A congressman, you say?
现在我只是你的酒伴
Right now, I'm just a drinking companion.
好吧  酒伴
Well, all right, companion.
来一杯吧
Have yourself a drink.
进来吧
Come on in.
这是一万美金
$10,000.
能买到什么服务
What will that get me?
我挺重口的
I mean, I'm kinky,
但恐怕我不是你想找的人
but I don't know if I'm the girl you're looking for.
你就是我要找的人
You're definitely the girl that I'm looking for.
请原谅
Excuse me.
我只想用这笔钱买你闭嘴
All I want for that money is your silence.
我什么
My what?
那天晚上跟你在一起的男人
The guy you were with the other night,
那个被逮捕的  你知道他是谁吗
the one who was arrested, do you know who he was?
你是说那位议员
You mean the congressman?
没有什么议员  也没有逮捕这回事
There was no congressman. There was no arrest.
没有那回事
None of that exists.
有的只是
All that exists
你面前的这沓钱
is the money sitting right there in front of you.
明白了吗
Do you understand?
明白了
Yeah.
很好
Good.
张嘴
Open your mouth.
这是我个人的消费
Last little bit's for me.
你在斥责我
You're scolding me.
有吗
Am I?
无声地斥责
You are, silently.
-是因为那台划船机吗  -你说呢
- Is it the rowing machine? - You tell me.
那就是了
It's the rowing machine.
-你都没用  -你怎么知道
- You haven't used it. - How do you know I haven't?
弗兰西斯
Francis.
你知道我不喜欢受人摆布
You know I don't like to be managed.
我没想摆布你
I'm not trying to manage you.
我只是不想守寡25年
I just don't want to outlive you by 25 years.
我每天在国会大厦肯定能走上三英里
I must walk three miles a day around that Capitol.
我经常步行
I'm constantly on my feet.
你知道脑力劳动有多消耗能量吗
And do you know how many calories the brain burns?
我不担心你的大脑
I'm not worried about your brain.
我担心的是你的心脏
It's your heart we're talking about.
好好用那台划船机
Use the machine.
她是对的
She's right.
我应该照顾好自己
I should take better care of myself.
但这是原则问题
But it's the principle.
我绝不受人
I won't be a slave to
或者免费电话能订购的东西摆布
anybody or anything you can order with a toll-free number.
我们这里实行共产主义
We share the wealth in this republic.
不是所有编辑人员都有参与吗
I thought the whole editorial team pitched in.
有时候如此  不过那次没有
Sometimes. Not that time, though.
但他肯定也写了一部分吧
But he must have written some of it?
不  全篇都是我写的
No. That was all me.
如果让人们认为是他写的呢
What if people thought he wrote it?
去他的  他是个骗子
Oh, fuck that. He's a fraud.
不  他还不如骗子呢  他就是个跳梁小丑
Nah, he's worse than a fraud. He's a fucking farce.
我跟你说
I'll tell you something.
他一度比我还疯狂
He used to be even more of a maniac than I am.
-是说吸毒吗  -不  是在政治上
- Chemicals? - No. Politics.
我们曾经彻夜长谈
Oh, we had some nights, man. Long conversations,
讨论危险的想法
dangerous fucking notions.
-比如呢  -什么都有  石油输出国组织
- Like what? - You name it-- OPEC,
皮诺切特  该死的食品券法案
Pinochet, the fucking Food Stamp Act.
皮诺切特: 1973年至1990年为智利军事独裁首脑
食品券法案: 1964年的一项法案  针对失业者和贫民发放粮票
后来祖国唱起了求偶之歌
Then the motherland sang her mating call.
哦  你能[美国国歌的首句歌词]
O say can you--
接着他就跑去布林茅尔为考律师埋头苦学
Next thing, he's cramming for the bar at Bryn Mawr
布林茅尔学院位于美国宾州  是一所百年名校
还别上了国旗胸针
and snapping on a flag pin.
布林茅尔有法学院吗
Does Bryn Mawr have a law school?
反正他自此正式加入了牵线木偶的队列
My point is, he started goose-stepping in the marionette parade.
左派右派  红营蓝营  民主共和
Left, right; red, blue; Democrat, Republican.
我们都被同一根线吊着
We're all dangling from the same strings.
《潘趣与朱迪》: 英国传统木偶戏
给这该死的木偶戏致命一击吧
Take a sledgehammer to the whole fucking Punch and Judy show.
这才是该做的
That's what's required.
我以为你很爱国呢
Thought you were a patriot.
没错  为数不多的爱国者
Fuck, yeah. One of the few.
-那你对公职人员有什么不满  -公职
- So what's wrong with public service? - Public service?
拜托  你得搞清楚你老大是谁
Come on. You gotta get a grip on who your masters are.
国际货币基金组织  世界银行
The I.M.F., the World Bank,
洛克菲勒三边委员会
the Rockefeller Trilateral Commission.
你为他们的爪牙提供资金
You bankroll their fucking death squads.
包括联邦应急管理局  烟酒军火管理局
It's called FEMA; it's called alcohol, tobacco, and firearms;
北约  还有边境管制
NATO; Border Control.
你以为卡特里娜飓风那次是办事不利吗
You think Katrina was incompetence?
那是精心策划的渎职
That was highly orchestrated negligence.
韦科事件: 1993年2月28日美国联邦执法人员围剿大卫邪教总部  造成惨案
看看韦科事件  国际特赦组织
Look at Waco, Amnesty International,
美国公民自由联盟
the ACLU.
全是障眼法  他们的手上沾满鲜血
Smokescreens-- all of them. Blood on their hands.
正因为如此啊
Well, exactly.
你想让我对公众撒谎
You want me to lie to the people.
我想让你替人民赶走一个伪君子
I want you to spare the people another hypocrite.
对你有什么好处
What's in it for you?
劝善惩恶
Poetic justice.
得了吧  你也是他们的一员
Oh, come on. You're one of them.
政府的探子能卷出这样的大麻吗
Can a corporate sellout roll a joint like this?
如果我同意帮你忙
If I wanted to do this thing,
我究竟该怎么做
how might I go about that, precisely?
还顺利吗
How did it go?
不少人都流了眼泪
There were a few tears here and there
还有些怒气
and some anger,
但都在预料之中
but nothing unexpected.
你今天也得离开公司  伊芙琳
I'm going to need you to leave us today, too, Evelyn.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
但我的决策方向容不得一丝质疑
I just can't have any doubt about the direction I'm taking.
你刚让我解雇了18名员工
You just had me fire 18 people.
我知道
I know.
我就坐在这个房间  和他们面对面
I sat across from them in this room,
我不得不告诉他们每个人
and I had to tell each and every one of--
我知道
I know.
我已经59岁了
I am 59 years old.
没人会雇我这把年纪的员工
Nobody hires anybody my age.
你要什么样的推荐信我都...
I will write you any kind of recommenda--
去应聘什么  收银员吗
To do what, bag groceries?
我该怎么告诉我女儿
What am I supposed to tell my daughter?
我很抱歉  伊芙琳  真心抱歉
I'm sorry, Evelyn. I truly am.
不  你没有  你压根不在乎
No, you're not. You don't give a fuck.
18个人啊  克莱尔
Eighteen people, Claire.
算上我的话  是19个
Nineteen, if you count me.
我要去
I have to...
我要打电话给我女儿了
I have to call my daughter.
我知道今天大家很难熬
I know today has been tough.
你们很多同事离开了
A lot of your colleagues have left,
而我欠你们一个解释
and I owe you an explanation.
今天离开我们的很多人
Many of those who left us today
帮我一手创建了净水计划
helped build the CWI from the ground up,
我对他们心怀感激
and I'm grateful to them.
但是我们要更上一层楼了
But it is time for us to evolve,
为达成这一目标
and to accomplish this,
我们必须做出艰难的抉择
we had to make hard choices
引进新人才
and bring in new people.
这就是今天的意义
That's what today was about.
有任何问题
You have any questions,
随时欢迎来找我
my door is always open.
国内和城市新闻没问题
I'm all good for national and metro.
如有必要  可以腾一点地方给政治新闻
We've got space for political if we need it.
简宁  有迈克尔・科恩的新消息吗
Janine, anything new on Michael Kern?
白宫在回避
The White House is dodging.
你采访不到任何人吗
You can't get anyone on record?
不只是我
Not just me.
他们在通气会上只字不提
They're shutting all of us down in the briefings.
所有人牙关紧闭  背景资料都不肯透露
No one is giving an inch, even on background.
与此同时  我正在策划
In the meantime, I'm working on a feature
关于政府外交政策议程的特辑
about the administration's foreign policy agenda.
它是如何从大选伊始慢慢改变
How it shifted from the start of the campaign,
-增加国防部开支  -说吧  佐伊
- increased D.O.D. spending, and-- - We see you, Zoe.
我能证明《公报》社论是科恩写的
I can link Kern directly to the Williams editorial.
-什么  -有个叫罗伊・科佩尼科的人
- What? - I've got a guy named Roy Kapeniak
他是科恩任主编时的一名编辑人员
who was on the editorial staff when Kern was there.
玩推特的娘们  搞什么鬼
Hey, Twitter twat, W.T.F.?
-等等  罗伊什么  -科佩尼科
- Wait, wait, wait. Roy what? - Kapeniak.
科恩的同班同学
A classmate of Kern's.
我有他的公开声明
I have him on record saying
称那篇社论出自科恩笔下
Kern wrote every word of the editorial.
进我办公室谈
Let's move this into my office.
佐伊  卢卡斯
Zoe, Lucas.
简宁
Janine.
请允许我  请允许我  最后一次
Let me-- let me, once and for all,
郑重声明
say this definitively:
社论不是我写的
I didn't author that editorial.
一句话  一个词  一个逗号  一个句点都不是
Not a single sentence, word, comma, or period.
如果我没记错  作者正是科佩尼科先生
If memory serves me, it was Mr. Kapeniak who wrote it.
科恩否认撰写社论  同班同学称科恩是反以社论作者
我无法理解他为什么声称是我写的
Why on earth he's trying to claim that I did is beyond me.
请允许我进一步阐明
Let me further say that I'm
我坚定地支持以色列国
a strong supporter of the State of Israel.
作为地区最稳定的国家
As the most stable country in the region
以及我们最可靠的同盟
and our strongest ally
弗兰克・安德伍德找凯茜
It's Frank Underwood for Cathy.
在任何的和平进程之中
...in any peace process,
如果没有以色列的稳定
because without the stability of Israel,
就不会有巴勒斯坦
there can be no Palestine.
快看CNN
CNN right now.
没有以色列就没有巴基斯坦
"Without Israel there can be no Palestine"?
-我在看了  -我想提醒科恩参议员
- I've got it on. - I would remind Senator Kern
巴勒斯坦历史可比以色列久远
that there was a Palestine long before there was an Israel.
他的言论不仅无知  还种族歧视
His comments are not only ignorant, they are racist.
准备好  凯茜  事态要开始急剧变化了
Get ready, Cathy. Things are about to move very quickly.
-他对于中东的理解  -好的
- ...his understanding of the Middle East-- - Okay.
-如此脱离现实  -我准备好了
- ...is so out of sync with reality... - I'm ready.
-彼得  站住  -等下
- Peter? No. Stop. - Uh, not now.
喂  你去哪了
Hey. Hey, where have you been?
天啊  你嗑药了
Oh, God, you're fucking high.
-没  我  -你绝对磕了  看你眼睛
- No. I-- - Yes, you are. Look at your eyes.
拜托了  别烦我
Oh, please, just lay off.
你保证过不会再这样了
You promised me it wouldn't be like this.
把今天剩下的事都取消掉
Cancel whatever I have for the rest of the day.
创新及行动奖  荣誉奖
科恩出局了
Kern is out.
他被踢出去了
They're tossing him?
严格地讲  是他退出  不过  没错
Technically, he'd withdraw himself, but yes.
我可以说"据白宫知情人士透露"吗
Can I say "A source close to the White House"?
不  这事你不要抢着报道
No. You let this story play out on its own time.
明早他们就会宣布
They'll announce in the morning.
不好意思  如果不是这篇  是什么新闻
I'm sorry. If not that, what story are we talking about?
凯瑟琳・杜兰特
Catherine Durant.
等科恩退出之后  你马上就说她会顶上来
As soon as Kern withdraws, you say she'll be the replacement.
-真的吗  -你写出来就成真了
- Is that true? - It will be after you write it.
罗伊・科佩尼科是你安排的
Roy Kapeniak was you.
随你怎么想  我不会发表意见
You might very well think that. I couldn't possibly comment.
你找到他了  让他给我打电话
You found him. You had him call me.
科佩尼科和科恩不过是开胃菜  巴恩斯小姐
Kapeniak and Kern were appetizers, Miss Barnes.
凯瑟琳・杜兰特才是主菜
Catherine Durant is the meal.
说出她的名字  凯瑟琳・杜兰特
Say that name: Catherine Durant.
一遍一遍地念叨
Say it over and over.
明天下午  写出来
Tomorrow afternoon, write it down,
然后就等着这名字
and then watch that name
从美国总统嘴里说出来吧
come out of the mouth of the President of the United States.
这是我们创造历史的契机
This is where we get to create.
巴恩斯小姐  别错过这班车了
Don't miss your train, Miss Barnes.
这是今晚最后一班了
It's the last one tonight.
《华盛顿先驱报》的佐伊・巴恩斯报道
Zoe Barnes with the Washington Herald now reporting,
杜兰特代替科恩成为提名人
据总统身边知情人士透露
quoting a source close to the president,
迈克尔・科恩本周早些时候退出之后
as saying that Senator Catherine Durant will likely be the
凯瑟琳・杜兰特参议员
new nominee for Secretary of State
很可能会代替他成为国务卿提名人
after Michael Kern's withdrawal earlier this week.
《华盛顿先驱报》称凯瑟琳・杜兰特将被提名为国务卿
白宫对总统是否会提名杜兰特
The White House has remained silent on whether the president
不予置评
will tap Durant for a nomination,
但是一项全国左格比民调显示
but a national Zogby Poll shows
杜兰特深受两党支持
wide support for Durant across party lines.
凯瑟琳・杜兰特在
Catherine Durant has served ten years
下任国务卿杜兰特
参议院外交委员会任职十年
on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee,
曾多次在南美执行外交任务
made numerous diplomatic missions to South America...
我们可以相信她
We can place our faith in her,
新提名人杜兰特
并深知一位负责  杰出
knowing that we have a responsible, experienced,
有经验的女性  在海外维护我国利益
brilliant woman representing our interests abroad.
中间路线  善于合作  善于辩护
Middle of the road, team player, strong in defense.
如果有哪位女性可以
If there's a woman that can
跟军方高层合作  那就是她
work with the joint chiefs, she's the one.
杜兰特可行  傻子都看得出来
Durant is the way to go. It's a no-brainer.
总统不应该再挑三拣四  选她就对了
The president should stop this pageant and simply make the call.
我们为什么还在讨论
Why are we still talking about,
仍未决定
他们是否会提名杜兰特
if they're going to nominate Durant?
他们为什么不赶紧定下
Why don't they just do it already
我们也可以停止猜测
so we can all stop talking about ifs
开始讨论杜兰特会何时
and start talking about when and what
如何制定怎样的外交政策
and how Durant's going to shape up foreign policy...
是历史吗
So, history?
是的
History.
真了不起  弗兰克
I'm very impressed, Frank.
好的  你点头了我就起草正式法案了
Good. With your go-ahead, I'll start the mock-up.
博奇和拉斯姆森看过这个了吗
Have Birch and Rasmussen seen this?
还没  我想先拿给你看一眼
Not yet. I wanted you to be the first to have a look.
我会找个时间让你给总统汇报
I'll schedule a time for you to fill in the president.
不用  那是你的工作  你去汇报就好
Oh, no, no, no. That is your turf, Linda. You should do that.
-谢谢  弗兰克  -荣幸之至  该谢你
- Thank you, Frank. - My pleasure. Thank you.
-对这一切  我万分抱歉  -不不不
- I so apologize for everything-- - No, no, no, n--
没必要
it's not necessary.
现在来谈正事
Now for the real meeting.
迈克尔・科恩怎么回事啊
So what is happening with Michael Kern?
简直是场噩梦
Oh, it's a total nightmare.
接下来要推选谁
You know who you're gonna tap next?
弗兰克  我们需要你留在议会
Frank, we still need you in the house--
不不不  我可不敢奢望
No, no, no. I wouldn't dream of it.
我们还要忙法案呢  我只是问问
We've got our education bill. I was just curious.
不知为什么  到处盛传
Somehow the rumor is flying around
我们将提名凯瑟琳・杜兰特
that we're gonna nominate Catherine Durant.
-你一定注意到了  -传言是真的吗
- I'm sure you've noticed. - Is the rumor true?
刚开始我们并未考虑她
Well, we weren't considering her at first,
但总统让我审查她
but the president asked me to have her vetted
以备我们选择她
in case we wanna go that route.
-有意思  -你觉得呢
- Interesting. - What do you think?
她不会是我的首选
Well, she wouldn't be my first choice--
谁会是你的首选
Who would be your first choice?
初选时她跟我们斗得厉害呢
She campaigned hard against us in the primaries.
这也是我的顾虑
That's my reservation.
但这会显得你顾全大局
But you'd show yourself above party politics,
而且我知道她会全力以赴的
and I know she'd work all the harder for it.
履历漂亮  在两党都受人尊敬
Decent experience, respect across the aisle.
所以她真的值得考虑吗
So you think we can seriously consider her?
反正不是最糟的选择
It's not the worst idea in the world.
你从哪搞来的消息
Where are you getting this shit?
什么
What?
你的报道
Your stories.
-我只是  -你跟谁上床了
- I was just- - Who are you fucking?
-没有  -少来了
- Nobody. - Oh, come on.
你不过是个小人物  现在瞧瞧你
You're a metro scrub, and now look at you.
你一定跟某个重要人物上床了
You'd have to be fucking somebody important.
我只是做了我的工作  简宁
I'm just doing my job, Janine.
失陪了
Excuse me.
都搞定了
All set.
-第一次远程采访吗  -是的  第一次
- Is this your first remote? - Yeah, it's my first time.
看着镜头  坐在椅子上别动
Right into the camera, don't shift in your seat,
说话音量别过高
and there's no reason to speak above a conversational volume.
麦克风录得到
The mic will pick you up.
-准备好了吗  -好了
- You all ready? - Yeah.
好的  注意呼吸
All right. Don't forget to breathe.
五  四
Five, four...
有请来自《华盛顿先驱报》的佐伊・巴恩斯
We'd like to welcome Zoe Barnes from the Washington Herald.
佐伊  感谢你加入我们
Zoe, thank you for joining us.
我非常荣幸  感谢你们邀请我
I'm very glad to be here. Thank you for having me.
你报道了教育法案  科恩的社论
You broke the education bill, the Kern editorial,
现在又是杜兰特
and now Durant.
能报道这种要闻我也很激动
I'm just thrilled to be reporting news that matters.
这都是团队合作的成果
And it's truly been a team effort.
《先驱报》的每个人都贡献了力量
Everyone at the Herald pitched in.
但是的  确实创造了许多第一次
But, yes, a lot of firsts.
第一次报道国家新闻  第一次...
First national story, first...
谢谢
Thank you.
我收工了
Calling it a night.
明天见  先生
See you tomorrow, sir.
但是的  确实创造了许多第一次
But, yes, a lot of firsts.
第一次报道国家新闻
First national story,
第一次头版署名
first front-page byline,
第一次电视采访
first TV interview.
我想向我妈妈招手
I would wave to my mom,
但摄像师不让我在座位上动
but the cameraman said not to shift in my seat.
真是风云突变
What a roller coaster.
真是不幸  科恩是个好人
It really is too bad. Kern was a good man.
-现在是凯瑟琳・杜兰特  -是的
- And now Catherine Durant. - Yes.
来得早不如来得巧
Right place, right time, I suppose.
-我们喜欢她吗  -非常喜欢
- We like her, don't we? - Very much.
问题是她是否像我们喜欢她一样喜欢桑科
Question is, does she like Sancorp as much as we like her?
我觉得值得压一注
I would say that that is a very good bet.
但话说回来  我不是个赌徒
But then again, I'm not a betting man.
不  你喜欢板上钉钉的事
No. You always like a sure thing.
如果有的话
When it avails itself.
-晚安  雷米  -晚安  弗兰克
- Good night, Remy. - Good night, Frank.
-后会有期  -希望不怎么再见了
- See you around. - Hopefully less and less now.
糟糕  我点错了
Oh, no. I charged the wrong thing.
-您要什么来着  -中杯脱因拿铁
- What did you have again? - A medium decaf latte.
中杯拿铁  脱因
Med lat, dec.
我不知道怎么退回去
I don't know how to get it to go back.
-点这个和这个  -这个吗
- This one and this one. - This one?
不是  我来吧
No. Let me do it.
您得退后  议员
I have to ask you to stay back, congressman.
怎么回事
What's going on?
这个家伙试图进入楼内
Some guy was trying to get into the building.
被我们拒绝后  他就开始撕衣服
When we said no, he started tearing his clothes off.
没人听得见  没人在乎
Nobody can hear you. Nobody cares about you.
这样做毫无用处
Nothing will come of this.
让这几位先生带你回家吧
Why don't you let these nice gentlemen take you home?
给他盖上  外面很冷
Cover him up. It's cold out here.
你听到了
You heard the congressman.
给他盖上
Cover him up.
弗兰西斯
Francis?
■
该剧在Netflix上线时
正值美国国务卿希拉里正式卸任  新任国务卿克里宣誓就职
奥巴马连任后  第一个记者招待会就明确表示
希望原驻联合国大使苏珊・赖斯接替希拉里担任新一任国务卿
却遭共和党很多议员强烈反对
因为赖斯曾经在2012年9月16号
接受5家电视台访问称  9月11日美国驻利比亚大使馆被袭击
是当地群众示威失控所致  但后来媒体发现
那其实是一场有组织有预谋的恐怖袭击  所以赖斯涉嫌误导公众
在被媒体和议员们猛烈攻击后  赖斯对外宣传放弃谋求国务卿职位
白宫重新选择参议员克里作提名人  克里非常顺利地被国会通过
与本剧情节不谋而合
■
本集片头之后  跟弗兰克吃饭的两个人分别是
议长  多数党领袖  而弗兰克是众议院多数党党鞭
三人依次是众议院多数党一把手  二把手和三把手
而现实中  现在华盛顿众议院是共和党把持
翻译  泽川
翻译  爱卿遛小鸟
翻译   cheeseflower
翻译  u油
翻译  妄想的绒布熊
翻译  木月
翻译  小蟹
翻译  ~某人
翻译  痒痒
翻译  小饭
时间轴  暮暮.Lee
顾问  老杜
后期  饿得慌
校对  草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第一季  第二集
人人影视倾情奉献
导演
大卫・芬奇